http://www.poolhost.com/index.asp?page=privacy.asp

Login
Members of your pool see banner ads. To remove banners for them Click Here
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or respond to a survey.
When ordering or registering on our site,
as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone
number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information
for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience(your information helps us to better respond to
your individual needs)
To improve our website(we continually strive
to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
To improve customer service(your information helps us to more effectively
respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
To
process transactionsYour information, whether public or
private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other
company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express
purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
To send periodic emailsThe email address you provide when you register
will only be used
to send you information and updates pertaining to your account including
sending your account password when you register or use our forgotten password retreival system.
You may receive emails from our site that include
company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we
include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How do we protect your information? We implement a variety of
security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted
via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers
database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such
systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.After a
transaction, your private information (credit card, billing address, etc.)
will not be stored on our servers.Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers
hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers
systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information We
use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of
advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that
we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with
third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors.
These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf
except to help us conduct and improve our business.Do we disclose any
information to outside parties? We do not sell, trade, or otherwise
transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include
trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or
servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.
We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply
with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or
safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other
parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Ad Banners
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/
Third party
links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or
services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy
policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities
of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and
welcome any feedback about these sites.California Online Privacy
Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have
taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy
Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside
parties without your consent.As part of the California Online Privacy
Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at
anytime by logging into out site and visiting the 'Edit User Info' page.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy
Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of
age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at
least 13 years old or older.Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our
website and not to information collected offline.Terms and
Conditions Please also visit our Terms and Conditions
section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing
the use of our website at our site's
Terms of Service page.
Your Consent By using our site, you consent to our
websites privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy If we decide to change our privacy
policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification
date below. This policy was last modified on 3/21/2016Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the
information below. 12340 Seal Beach Blvd., B148Seal Beach, CA 90740USAadmin@poolhost.com
Content Management Settings
About
PoolHost.com: The leader in sports pool hosting!
Follow Us On
Contact
Support Page
2000-2020 © PoolHost.com
FOR ENTERTAINMENT USE ONLY.
PoolHost.com is not affiliated in any way with the NFL, NBA, NHL, MLB, NCAA, UFC or any other professsional or collegiate sports team, league or association.
Any league, association or team names/logos are copyright of their respective owners.
